soxprospects.com 2010-08-23

# Privacy Policy | SoxProspects.com

|  |    
---|---  
  
  |   |   |    
---|---|---|---  
  |  | 

SoxProspects.com Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
**_  
__ Effective _** _**March 27, 2009**_

**Introduction**  
The privacy of our visitors to SoxProspects.com is important to us, as we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Here is a list of what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit SoxProspects.com, and how we safeguard that information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do not use cookies or web beacons to store information. We also use third party advertisements on SoxProspects.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing Massachusetts real estate ads to someone in Massachusetts, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Third-Party Hosts**  
SoxProspects.com uses third-parties to hosts the [online forum](http://forum-soxprospects.com/directory), the [news blog](http://news.soxprospects.com/), and the [ wiki](http://wiki.soxprospects.com/). SoxProspects.com is not responsible for information collected by those third parties. Those third parties' respective Privacy Policies can be found below:

Online Forum - **[ Yuku](http://www.yuku.com/homepage/privacy/t/Yuku-Privacy.html)**  
SoxProspects News - **[Google Blogger](http://www.blogger.com/privacy)**  
Wiki - **[ Wikispaces](http://www.wikispaces.com/Privacy+Notice)**

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@soxprospects.com](mailto:info@soxprospects.com).  
  
  |  | 

Sponsored By  

---  

Buy your [ MLB baseball tickets](http://www.coasttocoasttickets.com/mlb_baseball/) today.  Get [ Boston Red Sox tickets](http://www.coasttocoasttickets.com/mlb_baseball/redsox_tickets.shtml), [ Cubs tickets](http://www.coasttocoasttickets.com/mlb_baseball/cubs_tickets.shtml),   
and [ Athletics tickets](http://www.coasttocoasttickets.com/mlb_baseball/athletics_tickets.shtml).  We even have [ World Series tickets](http://www.coasttocoasttickets.com/mlb_baseball/worldseries_tickets.shtml)!  

Need football tickets? Visit [ SecureYourSeat.com](http://secureyourseat.com/)!  They have [ Tottenham Hotspur tickets](http://www.secureyourseat.com/tottenham-hotspur-tickets-c-574.html), [ Aston Villa tickets](http://www.secureyourseat.com/aston-villa-tickets-c-628.html), & [ Fulham tickets](http://www.secureyourseat.com/fulham-tickets-c-633.html). They also offer [ Premier League tickets](http://www.secureyourseat.com/premier-league-tickets-c-585.html) and [ Champions League tickets](http://www.secureyourseat.com/champions-league-tickets-c-656.html).  

Find  [ Red Sox seats](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/tix/boton-red-sox-tickets.aspx),  [ NFL tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/nfl.aspx),  [ Steeler football tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/tix/pittsburgh-steelers-tickets.aspx),  [ Florida football tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/tix/florida-gators-cf-tickets.aspx), the  [ NY Yankees schedule](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/tix/new-york-yankees-tickets.aspx),  [ NCAA football tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/collegefootball.aspx),  [ MLB playoff tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/mlb.aspx)   
and [ Philly Eagles tickets](http://www.ticketliquidator.com/tix/philadelphia-eagles-tickets.aspx).   

Order [ F](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/)[ootball tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/)[ in Europe](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/), such as [ Carling Cup tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/carling-cup-tickets.html),   
[ Champions League tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/champions-league-tickets.html), [ Community Shield tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/community-shield-tickets.html), [ English FA Cup tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/fa-cup-tickets.html), [ Liverpool tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/english-premiership/liverpool-tickets.html), and [ Chelsea tickets](http://www.livefootballtickets.com/english-premiership/fc-chelsea-tickets.html)   

Rankings updated every Friday  
during the season  
   
** Prospect Grading Legend**  

**SoxProspects Search**  

While visiting Boston, it's a must   
to get [ Fenway Park Tickets](http://www.fenwayticketking.com/) for events such as the Boston Red Sox. [ Red Sox tickets](http://www.fenwayticketking.com/boston_red_sox_tickets.html) at Fenway Park are very popular in New England. If you are lucky, you can get [ Red Sox vs Yankees tickets](http://www.fenwayticketking.com/red_sox_vs_new_york_yankees/index.html), which is the ultimate series.  

  |   
---|---  
  |  |   |   |   |   |   |    
---|---|---|---|---|---  
**   
 ** |  **   
 ** |  **   
 ** |  **   
 ** |  **   
 ** |  **   
 **  
  |   |   |   |   |    
  |  |  **Copyright © 2003-2010 SoxProspects, LLC**  
All Rights Reserved.  
**Last Updated** : Friday, July 09, 2010 11:31 AM   
**email** : [ info@soxprospects.com](mailto:info@soxprospects.com) | 

Site Map  

Privacy Policy

| 

SoxProspects.com is in no way affiliated with the Boston Red Sox, Pawtucket Red Sox,   
Portland Sea Dogs, Salem Red Sox, Greenville Drive, Lowell Spinners, GCL Red Sox,   
Major League Baseball, International League, Eastern League, Carolina League, South   
Atlantic League, New York-Penn League, Gulf Coast League, or Minor League Baseball.  
Images are proprietary, used with permission, or used pursuant to 17 U.S.C.  § 107.  

---|---|---  
  |   |   |   |   |
